sunbingo.co.uk 2006-04-19

# Sun Bingo - Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy and our promise to you** WE guarantee that access to your personal account information is restricted to you by your unique user name and password. All details are stored under the strictest supervision. We want to ensure complete trust from our players and to make playing Sun Bingo Online an enjoyable experience.

**Data Protection Act Registration** tombola (Alderney) Ltd is registered in Alderney under company number 1537. We comply with the Data Protection (Bailiwick Of Guernsey) Law 2001 registration number: 011311, we also comply with the UK data protection act 1998 registration number: PZ9208661. For a copy of our registrations under the Acts, please contact us via email at [support@sunbingo.co.uk](mailto:%20support@sunbingo.co.uk) Further information can also be found here: [http://www.dataprotection.gov.gg](http://www.dataprotection.gov.gg/) / [http://www.dpr.gov.uk](http://www.dpr.gov.uk/)

**Data Protection Notice** This notice explains how we will process your personal information.

The data controller will use your information together with other information for administration (including providing any goods, services or information you have requested), marketing, credit scoring, customer services and profiling your purchasing preferences. We will disclose your information to our service providers and agents for these purposes. We may keep your information for a reasonable period.

When you visit one of our websites, we send you a cookie. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes and we may use them to do a number of things: a) Cookies help us to recognise you when you next visit one of our websites and note the advertisements displayed to you. This allows us to tailor the advertisements we provide to your preferences. We may use the services of a third party and servers for this purpose. b) Cookies may be used to compile anonymous statistics related to the tale up or use of services, to patterns of browsing. A third party collects such data on our behalf to measure website performance. Information collected is aggregated for reporting purposes. No personally identifiable information is collected by this service. The use of this service assists us in measuring and improving the structure and ease of use of our websites.

You are not obliged to accept cookies and may modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please be aware that if you disable cookies, many services on our web sites will not be available to you.

We would like to share your information with organisations who are our business partners. We or they may contact you by mail, telephone or SMS or email to let you know about any goods, services or promotions which may be of interest to you. You may exercise your right to opt out of the use of your information for marketing purposes at any time by contacting us by the methods explained at the end of this notice.

By returning or submitting a form with your personal information to us, you consent to: a) Our processing your sensitive personal data such as health data for the above purposes. b) Our transferring your information to countries which do not provide the same level of data protection as the UK if necessary for the above purposes. If we do make such a transfer we will put a contract in place to ensure your information is protected.

When you give us information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them, to consent to the processing of the personal data, including sensitive personal data and to the transfer of their information abroad and to receive on their behalf any data protection notices.
